A Guide to the International Society for Third-Sector Research (ISTR) records FA1838
Rockefeller Archive Center
International Society for Third-Sector Research (ISTR) records
1990-2021
Rockefeller Archive Center
International Society for Third-Sector Research
Margery Daniels
FA1838
42.63 Cubic Feet 112 containers:111 letter document boxes, 1 legal document box
Arrangement
The International Society for Third-Sector Research records are organized into the following series:
Series 1: General Files Series 2: Board of Directors Series 2.1: General Series 2.2: Executive Committee Series 2.3: Elections Series 2.4: Board Meetings Series 3: Membership Series 4: Conference Planning Material Series 5: Conference Programs Series 6: Voluntas Series 7: Printed Material
Scope and Contents
The International Society for Third-Sector Research (ISTR) records contain the files of Executive Director, Margery Daniels. A large portion of these records document ISTR's international conferences which were held every two years. Also found within this collection are by-laws, meeting minutes, strategic planning reports, membership directories, newsletters, and a complete collection of ISTR's Voluntas publications.
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 5 years old are open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The International Society for Third-Sector Research records were donated to the RAC in 2022.
Nonprofit organization -- United States; Civil society; Philanthropy; Nonprofit organizations--Study and teaching--Global
- General Files, 1991-2021; 1; 14.9 Cubic Feet 38 letter document boxes, 1 legal document box
  - Cairo Centre, 2008 (Box 55, Folder 559)
  - Funding Proposals, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 562)
  - Potential Funders, 1993-1994 (Box 55, Folder 563)
  - Aga Khan Foundation, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 564)
  - Funding Proposals, 1997-1998 (Box 55, Folder 565)
  - Fundraising, 1997-1998 (Box 56, Folder 566)
  - Press Coverage, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 568)
  - Consultants, 1998 (Box 56, Folder 569)
  - Comparative Study on Peace and Conflict Resolution, 1998 (Box 56, Folder 570-571)
  - International Syllabi Project, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 572)
  - International Syllabi Project - Third Sector: Postgraduate Course, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 572)
  - International Syllabi Project - Prof. Dr. Karl-Heinz Boebenecker Syllabi Project, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 572)
  - Library Subscription Project, 1995-1997 (Box 56, Folder 573)
  - Asian Network Conference - Nippon Foundation Osaka Proposal, 1999-2001 (Box 57, Folder 574)
  - Nippon Foundation Proposals, 1999-2000 (Box 57, Folder 575)
  - Nippon Foundation Proposals, 2005-2006 (Box 70, Folder 750)
  - Nippon Foundation, 1997-1999 (Box 57, Folder 576)
  - Bylaws and Transition Decisions, 2017-2019 (Box 63, Folder 642)
  - Emerging Scholar Proposal, 2016 (Box 63, Folder 643)
  - Academic Freedom Statement (ISTR, the Association for Research on Nonprofit Organizations and Voluntary Actions (ARNOVA), the CINEFOGO Network of Excellence, and the EMES European Research Network), 2008-2017 (Box 63, Folder 644)
  - ISTR Africa Network PhD Seminar, Ghana, 2017 (Box 63, Folder 645)
  - EMES Cooperation, 2012-2013 (Box 63, Folder 647)
  - Financial Reports, 2008-2013 (Box 63, Folder 648)
  - Revenue Committee, 2014 (Box 63, Folder 650)
  - Hosting Committee, 2014 (Box 63, Folder 651)
  - Financial Information, 1995-1997 (Box 63, Folder 652)
  - David R. Stevenson Emerging Leaders Proposal, 2002-2003 (Box 63, Folder 654)
  - Johns Hopkins University Agreement, 2016-2017 (Box 63, Folder 657)
  - Transition Process, 2016-2018 (Box 63, Folder 658)
  - Friends of ISTR Europe, 2015-2016 (Box 63, Folder 659)
  - Friends of ISTR Bylaws, 2015-2016 (Box 63, Folder 660)
  - Alan Fowler, 1999-2003 (Box 63, Folder 661)
  - Andrés Thompson, 1995-1996 (Box 64, Folder 662)
  - ISTR Interim Governing Board, 1992-1993 (Box 64, Folder 663)
  - ISTR Bylaws 2018-2019, 2017-2018 (Box 64, Folder 666)
  - ISTR Bylaws Revision, 2017 (Box 64, Folder 667)
  - ISTR Initial Proposal to Institutions, 1992 (Box 64, Folder 668)
  - ISTR Bylaw Changes and Constitution, 1994-1995 (Box 64, Folder 669)
  - ISTR Inc. Minutes and By-Laws, 2018 (Box 112, Folder 1295)
  - Executive Direction Position, 1993 (Box 64, Folder 670)
  - Johns Hopkins University Agreement, 1992-1993 (Box 64, Folder 671)
  - David Lewis Injury Claim, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 672)
  - Scholarly Society Arrangement, 1998-1999 (Box 64, Folder 673)
  - Secretariat Location/Consultant, 2000-2001 (Box 65, Folder 674)
  - 501(c)(3) Status, 1995-2000 (Box 65, Folder 675)
  - ISTR Statement and Constitution, 1991 (Box 65, Folder 676)
  - Research and Publications Committee, undated (Box 65, Folder 677)
  - Fundraising Committee, 2003 (Box 65, Folder 678)
  - Journal Advertising, 2003 (Box 65, Folder 681)
  - Focus Groups, 2003 (Box 65, Folder 682)
  - American Sociological Association - Ed Hatcher, 1997-2003 (Box 65, Folder 686)
  - Website Consultants, 2002-2004 (Box 66, Folder 687)
  - ISTR-L (Listserv) and Website, 1995-1996 (Box 66, Folder 689)
  - Brochures, 1993-2001 (Box 66, Folder 690-691)
  - ISTR Brochure, 2001 (Box 66, Folder 691)
  - 2000 Annual Report (Box 66, Folder 693)
  - 2001 Annual Report, 2000-2001 (Box 66, Folder 694)
  - 2002 Annual Report, 2001-2002 (Box 66, Folder 695)
  - 2003 Annual Report, 2001-2004 (Box 66, Folder 696)
  - 2004 Annual Report, 2003-2005 (Box 66, Folder 697)
  - 2005 Annual Report, 2004-2006 (Box 66, Folder 698)
  - 2006 Annual Report, 2004-2006 (Box 67, Folder 699)
  - 2008 Annual Report, 2006-2007 (Box 67, Folder 700)
  - 1995 Progress Report Inserts (Box 67, Folder 701)
  - 1995 Progress Report Inserts, 1996-1997 (Box 67, Folder 702)
  - Affinity Groups, 2003-2008 (Box 68, Folder 717)
  - Affinity Groups - Arab Network, 2004-2005 (Box 68, Folder 718)
  - Affinity Groups - Millennium Development Goals, 2006 (Box 68, Folder 719)
  - Affinity Groups - Legal Issues Interest Group, 2007-2008 (Box 68, Folder 720)
  - International Council of Voluntarism/Civil Society/Social Economy Researcher Associations (ICSERA) - David H. Smith, 2011 (Box 68, Folder 721)
  - ISTR Archives, 2012-2013 (Box 68, Folder 727)
  - 2018 Yearbook, 2017; undated (Box 68, Folder 728)
  - 2017 Annual Report, 2018 (Box 68, Folder 729)
  - Social Media Reports, 2013 (Box 68, Folder 730)
  - Conflict of Interest Statement, 2009-2012 (Box 68, Folder 731)
  - Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) Network, 1997-2008 (Box 69, Folder 738-739)
  - Third Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) Network Meeting, Buenos Aires, 2001 September (Box 69, Folder 740-741)
  - New Members, Buenos Aires, undated (Box 69, Folder 742)
  - Ford Foundation - Mexico, 2010 (Box 69, Folder 743)
  - Latin American and the Caribbean (LAC) Network 1990s, 1997-2003 (Box 70, Folder 744)
  - Asia Pacific Regional Conference, 2013 (Box 70, Folder 745)
  - Asia Pacific Regional Conference, 2003 (Box 70, Folder 746)
  - Asia Pacific Network, Beijing, 2002-2003 (Box 70, Folder 747)
  - Asia Pacific Centre Directors, 2007-2008 (Box 70, Folder 748)
  - China Academic Centers, 2007-2009 (Box 70, Folder 749)
  - Asia Pacific 2015 Registrations (Box 70, Folder 751)
  - Asia Pacific Regional Network, 1998-2002 (Box 70, Folder 752)
  - Asia Pacific Meeting, Bangalore, 2005 (Box 70, Folder 753)
  - Asia Network, 1998-2001 (Box 71, Folder 754)
  - Asia Pacific Issues, 2000-2001 (Box 71, Folder 755)
  - Africa Regional Meeting, 2011 (Box 71, Folder 756)
  - Trust Africa Grant (90042132) - ISTR's 9th International Conference, 2010 (Box 71, Folder 757)
  - Voluntas Special Issue - Africa, 2010 October (Box 71, Folder 758)
  - Africa Network Paper Submissions, 2015 (Box 71, Folder 759)
  - Trust Africa Grant - Economic Spaces and Political Opportunities for African Civil Society Organizations, 2012-2014 (Box 71, Folder 760)
  - Trust Africa 2012 Reimbursement, 2013 (Box 71, Folder 761)
  - Trust Africa Reimbursement, 2011 (Box 71, Folder 762)
  - Africa Network, 1998-2003 (Box 71, Folder 763-765)
  - Second Africa Network Meeting, Nairobi, 2001 November (Box 72, Folder 766)
  - Africa Network Meeting, Berlin, 2004 March; 2003-2004 (Box 72, Folder 767)
  - Africa Network, Geneva, 1998-1999 (Box 72, Folder 768)
  - Scholars at Risk, 2016-2017 (Box 72, Folder 769)
  - 10th Anniversary Publication, 2001-2002 (Box 75, Folder 789-790)
  - Ford Regional Proposal - Full Time Coordinator, 2001-2002 (Box 75, Folder 791)
  - Ford Foundation - Jakarta, 2004-2005 (Box 75, Folder 792)
  - Himalaya Foundation, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 793)
  - Ford Foundation - India, 2006 (Box 75, Folder 794)
  - Japan Trip, 2008 December (Box 75, Folder 795)
  - German Marshall Fund, Turkey, 2009-2010 (Box 75, Folder 796)
  - Black Sea Trust, 2010 (Box 75, Folder 797)
  - Trust Africa - Contract, 2010 (Box 75, Folder 798)
  - Trust Africa, 2010-2011 (Box 75, Folder 799)
  - Ford Foundation - General Correspondence, 1993-2000 (Box 75, Folder 800)
  - Ford Foundation - Grant 2, 1995-1996, 1994-1997 (Box 76, Folder 801)
  - Ford Foundation - Grant 3, 1996-1998, 1995-1998 (Box 76, Folder 802)
  - Ford Foundation - Concept Paper, 2008 (Box 76, Folder 803)
  - Ford Foundation - Funding Proposal, 2005-2006 (Box 76, Folder 804)
  - Ford Foundation - Funding Proposal, 2006-2009 (Box 76, Folder 805-806)
  - Ford Foundation, 2009 (Box 76, Folder 807)
  - Ford Foundation - Funding Proposal, 2009-2011 (Box 76, Folder 808)
  - Ford Foundation - ISTR Progress Report, 1992 September 1-1993 June 30 (Box 76, Folder 809)
  - Ford Foundation - ISTR Progress Report, 1993 July 1-December 31 (Box 76, Folder 810)
  - Ford Foundation - ISTR Progress Report, 1994 January 1-December 31 (Box 76, Folder 811)
  - Latin America Network (LAC) - Anabel Cruz/Monica, 2003-2004 (Box 77, Folder 812)
  - W.K. Kellogg Foundation - Grant, 1999-2000 (Box 77, Folder 813)
  - W.K. Kellogg Foundation - 2005 Proposal, 2004-2007 (Box 77, Folder 814)
  - Africa Regional Meeting, 2015 (Box 77, Folder 815)
  - Japan Foundation - Award 90043227, 2010-2011 (Box 77, Folder 816)
  - Barry Knight - Strategic Planning Consultant, 2009 (Box 77, Folder 817)
  - W.K. Kellogg Foundation - Kellog Action Lab, New York City Meeting, 2008 (Box 77, Folder 818)
  - Homewood Institutional Review Board, 2009 (Box 77, Folder 819)
  - W.K. Kellogg Foundation - Kellogg Action Lab Grant, 2009 (Box 77, Folder 820)
  - W.K. Kellogg Foundation - Kellogg Action Lab, 2007-2010 (Box 77, Folder 821)
  - W.K. Kellogg Foundation - Proposal, 1998-1999 (Box 77, Folder 822)
  - W.K. Kellogg Foundation - 2004 Toronto Proposal, 2003-2005 (Box 77, Folder 823)
  - W.K. Kellogg Foundation - Scholarships, 1999-2002 (Box 78, Folder 824)
  - W.K. Kellogg Foundation - 2007 Report, 2007-2008 (Box 78, Folder 825)
  - W.K. Kellogg Foundation - Proposal, 2006-2008 (Box 78, Folder 826)
  - W.K. Kellogg Foundation - 2008-2009 Report, 2007-2010 (Box 78, Folder 827)
  - Ford Foundation - Funding Proposals, 1998-2000 (Box 78, Folder 828)
  - Southern African Grantmakers' Association, 1996 (Box 78, Folder 829)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1998-1999 (Box 78, Folder 830)
  - Foundation Center, 2013 (Box 78, Folder 831)
  - The Sasakawa Peace Foundation, 1993-2009 (Box 78, Folder 832)
  - Center for Global Partnership/Japan Foundation, 2010-2012 (Box 78, Folder 833)
  - Center for Global Partnership/Japan Foundation, 2013-2014 (Box 78, Folder 834)
  - Center for Global Partnership - Crisis and Its Implications for Civil Society and the Nonprofit Sector: Challenges and Opportunities in Asia and Beyond, 2015 (Box 79, Folder 835)
  - Center for Global Partnership - International Conference, 2010-2011 (Box 79, Folder 836)
  - Gates Foundation, 2009-2012 (Box 79, Folder 837)
  - Pears Foundation, 2010-2012 (Box 79, Folder 838)
  - Calouste Gulbenkian Foundation, 2010-2012 (Box 79, Folder 839)
  - Arab Foundation Forum, 2009 (Box 79, Folder 840)
  - Foundation for the Future - Regional Conference on Research on Civil Society Organisations, 2010 (Box 79, Folder 841)
  - Gulf Foundations, 2009 (Box 79, Folder 842)
  - Emirates Foundation, 2009 (Box 79, Folder 843)
  - Japan Concept Paper - The Impact of the Economic Crisis on Civil Society and Philanthropy in Asia and the United States, 2009 (Box 79, Folder 844)
  - Center for Global Partnership - Proposal, 2009-2010 (Box 79, Folder 845-846)
  - Center for Global Partnership - Voluntas Proposal, 2005-2006 (Box 79, Folder 847)
  - Japan Foundation - Proposal, 2007-2008 (Box 79, Folder 848)
  - Osaka Planning Workshop, 2009 (Box 79, Folder 849)
  - Center for Global Partnership - Grant Proposal, 2009-2010 (Box 79, Folder 850)
  - Africa Fundraising, Barcelona - Adefemi, Victor, 2007 (Box 80, Folder 851)
  - Ford Foundation - Barcelona - African Researchers, 2008-2009 (Box 80, Folder 852)
  - Ford Foundation - Barcelona - Mexican Researchers, 2008 (Box 80, Folder 853)
  - Ford Foundation - Barcelona - Indian Researchers, 2008 (Box 80, Folder 854)
  - Ford Foundation - Barcelona - Brazilian Researchers, 2008-2009 (Box 80, Folder 855)
  - Kellogg Scholarship, Barcelona, 2008 (Box 80, Folder 856)
  - Trust Africa Workshop, Istanbul, 2010 (Box 80, Folder 857)
  - Trust Africa, 2012-2014 (Box 80, Folder 858)
  - Africa Workshop, Muenster, 2013-2014 (Box 80, Folder 859)
  - Africa Network Proposals, 2011 (Box 80, Folder 860)
  - Ford Foundation - India, 2002-2004 (Box 80, Folder 861)
  - Ford Foundation, Institute of International Education (IIE) - South Africa, 2008-2011 (Box 80, Folder 862)
  - Ford Foundation, Institute of International Education (IIE) - Africa, 2011-2013 (Box 80, Folder 863)
  - Ford Foundation - Planning Grant, 2000-2003 (Box 80, Folder 864)
  - Ford Foundation, 2003-2004 (Box 81, Folder 865)
  - Körber Stiftung, 1995-1997 (Box 81, Folder 866)
  - Ford Foundation - Nairobi, 1998-1999 (Box 81, Folder 867)
  - Ford Foundation - Africa Grant, 2001-2002 (Box 81, Folder 868)
  - Ford Foundation - Africa Report, 2004 (Box 81, Folder 869)
  - Latin America, 1996-1998 (Box 82, Folder 884)
  - Asia Pacific Network Conference, 2001-2002 (Box 82, Folder 885)
    Scope and Contents
    Original folder title: Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) Network
  - Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) Network and Inter-American Foundation (IAF), 2005-2007 (Box 82, Folder 886)
  - Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) Network, 2002-2003 (Box 82, Folder 887)
  - Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) Network - Bahia ISTR Report, 1999-2007 (Box 82, Folder 888)
  - Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) Network - Bahia, 1998-2007 (Box 82, Folder 889)
  - Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) Network - 8th Conference, Buenos Aires, 2011 (Box 82, Folder 890)
  - Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) Network - Conference, 2013 (Box 83, Folder 891)
  - Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) Network - Registrations, 2015 (Box 83, Folder 892)
  - Central and Eastern European Network, 1997-2008 (Box 83, Folder 893)
  - EMES European Network, 2005-2008 (Box 83, Folder 894)
  - Economic Theories of Nonprofit Organizations - Voluntas Symposium, 1994-1995 (Box 83, Folder 895)
  - ISTR Centre Directors Group, 2004-2005 (Box 83, Folder 896-897)
  - Scholarship Affinity Group, 1994-1996 (Box 83, Folder 898)
  - German Speaking Affinity Group, 1996 (Box 83, Folder 899)
  - W.K. Kellogg Foundation, 1994-1995 (Box 84, Folder 906)
  - W.K. Kellogg Foundation, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 907)
  - W.K. Kellogg Foundation, 1997-1998 (Box 84, Folder 908)
  - Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) Network - Meeting, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 909)
  - Mott Foundation - Grant 92-334, 1992-1994 (Box 84, Folder 910)
  - Mott Foundation - ISTR Progress Report, 1993 January-June (Box 84, Folder 911)
  - Mott Foundation - ISTR Progress Report, 1993 July-December (Box 84, Folder 912)
  - Mott Foundation - Grant 93-270, 1993-1994 (Box 85, Folder 913)
  - Mott Foundation - ISTR Progress Report, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 914)
  - Mott Foundation - Grant 94-251, 1994-1995 (Box 85, Folder 915)
  - Mott Foundation - Grant 96-236, 1995-1998 (Box 85, Folder 916)
  - Mott Foundation - Reports, 1996-2001 (Box 85, Folder 917)
  - Mott Foundation - Grant 98-403, 1998-2001 (Box 85, Folder 918)
  - Mott Foundation - Proposal, 2001-2002 (Box 85, Folder 919)
  - Mott Foundation - Reports, 2002-2007 (Box 85, Folder 920)
  - Mott Foundation - Proposal, 2002-2004 (Box 85, Folder 921)
  - Mott Foundation - Proposal, 2004-2006 (Box 85, Folder 922)
  - Mott Foundation - Proposal, 2007-2008 (Box 86, Folder 923)
  - Mott Foundation, 2009-2010 (Box 86, Folder 924)
  - Mott Foundation - Proposal, 2010-2012 (Box 86, Folder 925)
  - Mott Foundation, 2012-2014 (Box 86, Folder 926)
  - Mott Foundation, 2014-2016 (Box 86, Folder 927)
  - Mott Foundation, 2016-2017 (Box 86, Folder 928)
  - Mott Foundation - Proposal, 2016-2019 (Box 86, Folder 929)
  - Mott Foundation, 2017-2018 (Box 86, Folder 930)
  - Mott Foundation - Subgrant, 2018-2020 (Box 86, Folder 931)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted - Open in 2025
  - Mott Foundation - Report, 2019 (Box 86, Folder 932)
  - Mott Foundation, 2020-2021 (Box 86, Folder 933)
    Restricted - Open in 2026
  - Funding Proposals, 1992-1993 (Box 93, Folder 1020)
  - ISTR Report: A Call from the South, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 1021)
  - ISTR Report: Globalization, Marginalization and the Retreat of the State in Africa, 1997 (Box 93, Folder 1022)
  - ISTR Report: Presidential Address on the Occasion of the General Assembly of ISTR (Part 1), 1998 (Box 93, Folder 1023)
  - ISTR Report: Strategic Directions 2000-2005, 1999 (Box 93, Folder 1024)
  - ISTR Report: Latin American Perspectives on the Third Sector, 2000 (Box 93, Folder 1025)
  - Annual ISTR Report, 2000 (Box 93, Folder 1026)
  - Annual ISTR Report, 2001 (Box 93, Folder 1027)
  - ISTR Report: Second ISTR Asia and Pacific Regional Conference, 2001 (Box 93, Folder 1028)
  - Annual ISTR Report, 2002 (Box 93, Folder 1029)
  - ISTR Report: Questioning Civil Society in Africa, 2002 (Box 93, Folder 1030)
  - ISTR Report: Third ISTR Asia and Pacific Regional Conference: A Review of the Papers, 2003 (Box 93, Folder 1031)
  - ISTR Report: The Role of Civil Society in Development Processes: A Multi-Stakeholder Dialogue, 2004 (Box 93, Folder 1032)
  - ISTR Report: Obstacle, Bridge, or Promised Land? The Role of Civil Society in the Challenges Confronting Africa, 2005 (Box 93, Folder 1033)
  - Voluntas Report, 2008 (Box 93, Folder 1034)
  - European Foundation Centre, 2016 (Box 93, Folder 1035)
  - European Foundation Centre - Proposal, 2014-2015 (Box 93, Folder 1036)
  - Journal Proposal - Dennis Young, 2006 (Box 93, Folder 1037)
  - Centre Directors, 2005-2006 (Box 93, Folder 1038)
  - Centre Director Profiles, 2006-2011 (Box 93, Folder 1039)
  - Centre Directors Meeting, Siena, 2012 (Box 94, Folder 1040)
  - National Academic Centers Council, Istanbul, 2009-2010 (Box 94, Folder 1041)
  - Independent Research Centers, 2007-2008 (Box 94, Folder 1042)
  - Africa Network Meeting, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 1043)
  - Africa Workshop, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 1044)
  - Civil Society Researchers in Africa Proposal, 1996-1997 (Box 94, Folder 1045)
  - Africa Workshop Papers, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 1046)
  - Africa Network Questionnaire, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 1047)
  - Africa Network, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 1048)
  - Africa Affinity Group, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 1049)
  - The State of Research on the Third Sector and Civil Society in Latin America and the Caribbean, Olga Lucia Torro, 2001 (Box 98, Folder 1100-1101)
  - Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) Network - Fund Meeting, Buenos Aires, 2001 (Box 98, Folder 1102)
  - Smulovitz, Catalina, 1996-1997 (Box 98, Folder 1103)
  - Ritsumeikan Trust, 2009 (Box 98, Folder 1104)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 2005 (Box 99, Folder 1105)
  - Skoll Foundation, 2005 (Box 99, Folder 1106)
  - Suntory Foundation, 2009 (Box 99, Folder 1107)
  - Suntory Foundation - Trust for Civil Society in Central and Eastern Europe - Annual Report, 2006 (Box 99, Folder 1108)
    Open for research. Digital access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - William and Flora Hewlett Foundation, 2004-2005 (Box 99, Folder 1108)
  - Medellin, Colombia, 2017-2019 (Box 99, Folder 1109)
  - Asia Pacific PhD Seminar, 2019 (Box 99, Folder 1110)
  - Asia Pacific Conference Program, 2019 (Box 99, Folder 1111)
  - Asia Pacific Conference, 2018-2019 (Box 99, Folder 1112)
  - European Research Network on Philanthropy (ENOP) Panel, 2015 (Box 99, Folder 1113)
  - Friends of ISTR, 2015 (Box 99, Folder 1114)
  - Strategic Taskforce, 2014-2015 (Box 99, Folder 1115)
  - European Research Network on Philanthropy (ENOP), 2017 (Box 99, Folder 1116)
  - Star Alliance, 2015-2016 (Box 99, Folder 1117)
  - Regional Networks, 2010 (Box 100, Folder 1125)
  - Ford Foundation - Mexico Grant, 2018 (Box 100, Folder 1126)
  - Ford Foundation - Chile Grant, 2000-2001 (Box 100, Folder 1127)
  - Ford Foundation - East Africa, 2019 (Box 100, Folder 1128)
  - Ford Foundation - West Africa, 2019 (Box 100, Folder 1129)
  - Ford Foundation - Institute of International Education (IIE) and Latin American and the Caribbean (LAC) Network, 2019 (Box 100, Folder 1130)
  - Ford Foundation - Asia, 2019 (Box 100, Folder 1131)
  - Dunhe Foundation, 2018-2019 (Box 100, Folder 1132)
  - Statement of Support for Kinman Chan, 2018-2019 (Box 100, Folder 1133)
  - Asia Pacific Meeting, Tokyo, 2015 (Box 100, Folder 1134)
  - East Asia Network - Memorandum of Understanding, 2019 (Box 100, Folder 1135)
  - Japan NPO Research Association - Memorandum of Understanding, 2018 (Box 100, Folder 1136)
  - Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) Network, 2018-2019 (Box 100, Folder 1137)
  - Collaboration Agreements, 2015 (Box 100, Folder 1138)
  - Global Philanthropy Symposium, 2013-2015 (Box 100, Folder 1139)
  - Beijing Meetings, 2013 (Box 100, Folder 1140)
  - Authoritarian Regimes, 2015 (Box 100, Folder 1141)
  - Thematic Groups, 2016 (Box 101, Folder 1142)
  - Social Science and Humanities Research Council of Canada (SSHRC) Partnership, 2016 (Box 101, Folder 1143)
  - Dissertation Award, 2004-2006 (Box 101, Folder 1144)
  - Dissertation Letters, 2006 (Box 101, Folder 1145)
  - ISTR Dissertation Award Proposal, 2004-2006 (Box 101, Folder 1146)
  - Young Scholar Dissertation Award, 2007-2008 (Box 101, Folder 1147)
  - Emerging Scholar Dissertation, 2009-2016 (Box 101, Folder 1148)
  - Emerging Scholar Award 2010, 2009-2010 (Box 101, Folder 1149)
  - Emerging Scholar Award 2012, 2011-2012 (Box 101, Folder 1150)
  - Emerging Scholar Award 2014, 2013-2014 (Box 101, Folder 1151)
  - Awards, 2014 (Box 101, Folder 1152)
  - Best Paper Award, 2013-2015 (Box 101, Folder 1153)
  - Best Paper Award, 2014-2015 (Box 101, Folder 1154)
  - Best Paper Award, 2017-2018 (Box 101, Folder 1155)
  - Emerging Scholar Award 2016, 2014-2016 (Box 101, Folder 1156)
  - Dissertation Award 2018, 2017-2018 (Box 101, Folder 1157)
  - Latin America Meetings, undated (Box 101, Folder 1158)
  - Asia Meetings, 1999-2015 (Box 101, Folder 1159)
  - IV ISTR Asia-Pacific Conference, India, 2005 (Box 103, Folder 1173)
  - Asia-Pacific Conference, 2012 (Box 103, Folder 1174)
  - 6th Asia Pacific Regional Conference, Taiwan, 2007-2009 (Box 103, Folder 1175)
  - Asia Pacific Conference, Indonesia, 2010-2011 (Box 103, Folder 1176)
  - Africa, 2011-2013 (Box 103, Folder 1177)
  - Africa Network, 2005-2010 (Box 103, Folder 1178)
  - Africa Regional Meeting, 2009-2011 (Box 103, Folder 1179)